https://williams-syndrome.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – Williams Syndrome Foundation
Skip to content
Home
Williams Syndrome?
0
No products in the basket.
Log In
Donate
0
Basket
No products in the basket.
Log In
Donate
WSF website privacy policy
We collect certain information or data about you when you use the Williams Syndrome Foundation website. This policy explains how the data you provide is processed. This includes:
questions, queries or feedback you leave, including your email address if you send an email to us
your IP address, and details of which version of web browser you used
information on how you use the site, using cookies and page tagging techniques to help us improve the website
details to allow you to access our services and transactions, e.g. an email address (you’ll always be told when this information is being collected, and it will only be used for the purpose you provide it for)
This helps us to:
improve the site by monitoring how you use it
respond to any feedback you send us, if you’ve asked us to
provide you with information about our services if you want it
We can’t personally identify you using your data.
All data you supply via this website is being processed under the responsibility of the Williams Syndrome Foundation Limited, registered with the Charity Commission in England and Wales (Charitable Number 281014). You may contact us here: enquiries@williams-syndrome.org.uk
The Williams Syndrome Foundation will act as the data controller for the reasons numbered below. No other third party (save, where you have consented on becoming a member, for bona fide researchers approved by the WSF) will access this data, unless you explicitly agree otherwise .  We act as the data controller for all information provided by you initially through this website.
Cookies.The website uses a session cookie to store your personal data when filling out multiple forms. Depending on your privacy settings, such cookies will be accepted by your browser. The session cookie will not transfer information to third parties.
Analytics.The Williams Syndrome Foundation may run analytics to understand more about the visitors to our website.
Data sharing.The Williams Syndrome Foundation shall never voluntarily share your information with a third party for their own use, except as indicated under (2) above.
Access to your data.Under the Data Protection Act, you may at any time request a copy of the information we hold on you by e-mailing us at the above stated addresses. Any requests for deletion or correction of your personal data can also be obtained via this address.
enquiries@williams-syndrome.org.uk
Click Here to View our WSF Members Privacy Policy
WILLIAMS SYNDROME FOUNDATION LTD Registered Charity Number 281014
Tel: 0208 5671374
GET IN TOUCH Membership enquiries 07838 348577
General enquiries 0208 567 1374
Office and Communications 07392 332390
enquiries@williams-syndrome.org.uk
DELIVERY ADDRESS Williams Syndrome Foundation, Box 103, Charter House, Lord Montgomery Way, Portsmouth, PO1 2SN.
Please post all correspondence to the  Portsmouth address. Any post sent to the old Tonbridge address will not be passed on.
Home
What is Williams Syndrome?
About WSF
Williams People
Shop
News & Events
Data Protection
Privacy
Copyright 2020 © Williams Syndrome Foundation. Website by Complete Digital
Home
Williams Syndrome?
Williams Syndrome Explained
FAQs
Clinical Guidelines & Research Information
About WSF
What is WSF
History
Commitee & Staff
Professional Advisory Panel
Donate
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Always Enabled
Login
Username or email address *
Password *
Login
Remember me
Lost your password?
